We sell motocross training, we hold five day camps.
One day is $300, which is probably not enough.
The five day is $1,200, which is definitely not enough.
Why can't you charge more?
I definitely can.
The reason I haven't is because I started riding
dirt bikes when I was two.
I turned pro when I was 16.
Impact, et cetera, helped people I want to multiply.
My family had no money, so I didn't want to out-price
the people that were me.
Do you make content, is that the primary way
that you get customers?
Yeah.
Okay, so you do that for free.
And those people get that for free.
Everything's free, yeah.
Right, we have 22 million subscribers.
There's 100 people here.
A lot of people get you for free.
You will never help in person, even a tiny fraction
of a percent of the people that you've helped for free.
You will be able to monetize 1% of the people,
maybe, if you're lucky, in the way media exists today.
If you were to turn this into a gigantic company,
do you think you'd make a bigger impact than you do now?
Yes.
Right, and in order to do that, it takes money.
You can serve the person who can't afford it for free,
and then you serve the people who can't afford it
for the correct price.